ibps.in 2009-05-06

# :: Welcome to IBPS ::

Privacy Policy  

#### 1.1 Personally identifiable information

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about the visitors to this website.  
We do not allow third-party content (such as advertisements) on this website that attempts to collect any personally identifiable information or attempts to track users' browsing habits across the Internet.

#### 1.2 "Cookies"

We may employ so-called "cookies" -- small, browser-side text files -- in order to facilitate better navigation and usability of this website, to enhance user experience of this website. All cookies used are anonymous and do not store any personally identifiable information.

#### 1.3 Personally identifiable information

We receive personally identifiable information, such as Name, Address, Email address, from those users who choose to apply for the recruitment for the posts through some of our pages specifically placed for the sole purpose of Recruitment Process. Information collected is solely used for the purpose of communication with the users generally the candidates and covers the information such as their eligibility for candidature, Exam Dates, Exam Venue for the given posts.   
We may also receive personally identifiable information from those users who choose to contact us with requests for information, referral requests, service enquiries, comments, feedback.

#### 1.4 Information disclosure to third parties

Personally identifiable information as per point 1.3 is treated as strictly confidential. The contents of any communication transmitted are treated as strictly confidential, proprietary and restricted.  
Your name, email, telephone or fax number or any other personal information, or the contents of any communication transmitted is never shared with, sold, rented, lent or otherwise disclosed to any third-party party. If the above information is collected for recruitment for any Organization serviced by IBPS, information is passed on solely for the purpose of your candidature for the Post you have applied for.  
We follow strict guidelines in order to prevent unauthorized access to confidential data.
